(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ちょこ先生はてぇてぇに囲まれたい ～癒月ちょこ生誕祭2023～
Choco-sensei wants to be surrounded by 'Teetee' ~Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2023~
Are you ready?
NoDistance 作詞・作曲：涼木シンジ (KEYTONE)
NoDistance / Lyrics & Composition: Shinji Suzuki (KEYTONE)
言葉を並べては　見なほら、ララヤ
Words lined up, see? La la ya.
理屈だなんて　ゴミ箱へ
Logics and such, into the trash.
身に覚えあるんでしょう　アンサー
You have a vague idea, don't you? Answer.
チク、チク、痛いのね
Prick, prick, it hurts, doesn't it?
エゴイズムに踊らされて
Dancing to the tune of egoism.
蝕まれていく　アレ？アレ？
Being eaten away. Oh? Oh?
地に焼き付けて　悪までも
Sear it into the ground, even for evil.
癒してあげましょう　お目覚めですか？
Let me heal you. Are you awake?
Ding Dong Ding Dong　響かせ Ding Dong
Ding Dong Ding Dong, let it echo, Ding Dong.
笑いな　ハッハッ　吐き捨てて
Laugh, ha-ha, spit it out.
Ding Dong Ding Dong　鳴らせよ Ding Dong
Ding Dong Ding Dong, ring it, Ding Dong.
病むのが先か　止むのが先か
Will you break first? Or will it stop first?
噛みつきゃしないわ
I'm not going to bite you.
慰めもしないわ
I'm not going to comfort you either.
私のものね
You belong to me, don't you?
飽きたら　NoDistance
When you're bored, NoDistance.
闇に紛れ甘いチョコレート捨てて
Hiding in the dark, throw away the sweet chocolate.
古びた鎖繋いではくどいて
Connecting old chains, courting.
仮の姿化けて瞳を貸して
Disguising yourself, lend me your eyes.
傷が痛むのね
The wound hurts, doesn't it?
メカニズムに踊らされて
Dancing to the tune of the mechanism.
失われていく　アレ？アレ？
Fading away. Oh? Oh?
間違えても正しくても
Whether you're wrong or right.
妖してあげましょう　あ、まだ
Let me bewitch you. Oh, not yet...
ダメですか？
...is it no good?
Ding Dong Ding Dong　狂わせ Ding Dong
Ding Dong Ding Dong, drive them crazy, Ding Dong.
最後に　ハッハッ　吐き捨てて
In the end, ha-ha, spit it out.
Ding Dong Ding Dong　鳴らせよ Ding Dong
Ding Dong Ding Dong, ring it, Ding Dong.
迷わずに
Without hesitation,
鳴動
Rindou,
醒める前に
before waking up.
口付けを
Give me a kiss,
鳴動 鳴動
Rindou, Rindou.
響かせ 鳴動
Let it echo, Rindou.
笑え アハハハと叫べ
Laugh, and shout "Ahahaha!"
鳴動 鳴動
Rindou, Rindou.
鳴らせよ 鳴動
Ring it out, Rindou.
病むのが先か
Will I fall ill first,
止むのが先か
or will it stop first?
噛みつきはしないわ
I won't bite you.
慰めもしないわ
I won't comfort you either.
私の物ね
You are mine.
飽きたら No distance
Once I'm bored, No distance.
撫でんな 作詞・作曲 マグネタイト
Nadennna - Lyrics & Composition: Magnetite
アタマから手ほどけて 手ほどけて
Unraveling from the head, unraveling.
撫でたりしないで
Don't stroke me.
あなたが 私だけじゃなくなっちゃうの
You won't be mine alone anymore.
もう耐えらんない
I can't stand it anymore.
毎回暗がりがガスるチカチカ
Every time the darkness flickers like gas.
住んでいた家帰るの嫌じゃんか
I hate going back to the house I lived in.
「やめときなさい」って言われてもさ
Even if I'm told to "stop it,"
独りじゃ寂しいし 当たり
it's lonely being alone, right?
アンタイしたって無駄って分かって
Knowing that resisting is useless.
世論食らったマシュと地雷ジャンセ
Mashing public opinion and landmines.
独りできずけて 勘違いじゃ
Noticing it alone, it's not a mistake.
今もあんたなんか知らない
I still don't know someone like you.
アタマから手ほどけて 手ほどけて
Unraveling from the head, unraveling.
撫でたりしないで
Don't stroke me.
私が私じゃなくなっちゃう前に
Before I'm not myself anymore,
やめてよ
stop it.
目を開けて 目を開けて
Open your eyes, open your eyes.
ちゃんと私を見て
Look at me properly.
あなたが「私だけ」じゃなくなっちゃうの
You won't be "mine alone" anymore.
もう耐えらんない
I can't stand it anymore.
大概疑い合ってまたイライラ
Mostly doubting each other and getting frustrated again.
住んでいた家帰りたくなってた
I started wanting to go back to the house I lived in.
離れて馬鹿々々しい 独りじゃ辛いから
Being apart is silly, because it's hard being alone.
お願い
Please.
ああもう そっちがその気なら
Ah, enough! If that's how you're going to be,
真っ赤な目でとかふわっと尻尾で拘束しちゃっていいですかって
may I restrain you with red eyes or a fluffy tail?
独りじゃ気づかない ああそうですか
I don't notice it alone, oh is that so.
じゃあ 今もあんたなんか知らない
Well, I still don't know someone like you.
何も言わないで 聴いて そばにいて
Don't say anything, listen, stay by my side.
それでいいから
That's enough.
私がただ独りで悩んでても
Even if I'm just worrying alone,
構わないで
don't mind me.
もう！手ほどけて 手ほどけて
Geez! Unraveling, unraveling.
撫でたりしないで
Don't stroke me.
私が私じゃなくなっちゃう前に やめてよ
Before I'm not myself anymore, stop it.
目を開けて 目を開けて
Open your eyes, open your eyes.
ちゃんと私を見て
Look at me properly.
あなたが誰かと楽しそうにしてるの
You looking happy with someone else,
嫌なだけだよ
I just hate it.
勘違いしないでよ
Don't misunderstand.
撫でてほしいの
I want you to stroke me.
あなたが「私だけ」じゃなくなっちゃうの
You won't be "mine alone" anymore.
もう耐えらんない
I can't stand it anymore.
はーい！ということでみんな、今日は来てくれてありがとう！
Hi! So everyone, thank you for coming today!
や、今回のちょこのお誕生日ライブは、なんと！
Now, this Choco birthday live is, surprisingly!
や、このね、サムネにも書いてあるんですけど「ちょこ先生はてぇてぇに囲まれたい」
Now, as it says in this thumbnail, "Choco-sensei wants to be surrounded by teete."
癒月ちょこ生誕祭2023ということで！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2023!
なんとなんとね、豪華ゲスト！
Surprisingly, we have some gorgeous guests!
まぁサムネでバレちゃってるんですけど
Well, they're already spoiled by the thumbnail,
まぁどの組み合わせになるのかはね、ちょこの推しメンということでお楽しみにしててくださーい！
but look forward to seeing which combinations they'll be in, as they're Choco's favorites!
そしてそして、今回の配信のハッシュタグこちら！
And then, the hashtag for this stream is this!
あ、違う、こっちだ。こちら！
Ah, no, it's this way. This!
#癒月ちょこ生誕祭2023
#YuzukiChocoBirthdayLive2023
＃癒月ちょこ生誕祭2023で、あの...2023で、あ...2023で呟いてください！
Please tweet with #YuzukiChocoBirthdayLive2023! Um... with 2023... ah... with 2023!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
ということで、それではですね...
So, then...
早速、ゲストパートの方に移っていきましょー！
Let's move on to the guest part right away!
呼んできてまーす！
I'll go call them in!
ちょっと待っててね。
Wait just a moment.
チョコレイト・ディスコ
作詞・作曲 中田ヤスタカ
Chocolate Disco
Lyrics & Composition: Yasutaka Nakata
チョコレイト・ディスコ
Chocolate Disco
計算する女の子
Girls who calculate
期待してる男の子
Boys who are expecting
ときめいてる女の子
Girls who are excited
気にしないふり男の子
Boys who pretend not to care
バレンタインが近づいて
Valentine's Day is approaching
デパートの地下も揺れる
The department store basements are also shaking
計算する女の子
Girls who calculate
期待してる男の子
Boys who are expecting
お願い 想いが 届くようにね
Please, let my feelings reach them
とても 心 こめた 甘いの
Something sweet, put my whole heart into
お願い 想いが 届くといいな
Please, I hope my feelings reach them
対決の日は来た
The day of the showdown has come
チョコレイト・ディスコ
Chocolate Disco
計算する女の子
Girls who calculate
期待してる男の子
Boys who are expecting
ときめいてる女の子
Girls who are excited
気にしないふり男の子
Boys who pretend not to care
お願い 想いが 届くようにね
Please, let my feelings reach them
とても 心 こめた 甘いの
Something sweet, put my whole heart into
お願い 想いが 届くといいな
Please, I hope my feelings reach them
なぜか 教室 ダンスフロアに
For some reason, the classroom turns into a dance floor
チョコレイト・ディスコ
Chocolate Disco
ディスコ、ディスコ
Disco, disco
チョコレイト・ディスコ
Chocolate Disco
ディスコ、ディスコ
Disco, disco
チョコレイト・ディスコ
Chocolate Disco
ディスコ、ディスコ
Disco, disco
チョコレイト・ディスコ
Chocolate Disco
ディスコ
Disco
はーい！ということで！
Haaay! And so!
おええええ！/イエーイ！
Whoooo! / Yay!
いいな、このステージ。
This stage is nice.
ね。わためちゃんのステージ、借りちゃいました。
Right. We borrowed Watame-chan's stage.
ありがとうございます。イエーイ！
Thank you. Yay!
ということで、我々トップバッター？
So, are we the opening act?
そうです。
That's right.
トップバッターらしいぞ。
Seems like we're the opening act.
「てぇてぇに囲まれたい」第1弾トップバッターは...
'To be surrounded by Teete-ness' first opening act is...
ししわたコンビです！
The ShishiWata duo!
イエーイ！挟んじゃうぞー！
Yay! We're gonna sandwich you!
お尻で挟んじゃうぞー！物理的に！
We're gonna sandwich you with our butts! Physically!
物理的に挟まれてるんだけど。
I'm being physically sandwiched.
ちょこ先生挟んじゃったんだけど。
We totally sandwiched Choco-sensei.
チョコ先生なんか、今日はなんか聞きたいことあったりする？
Choco-sen, is there anything you'd like to ask today?
あ、ちょっと、やっぱ獅白わためと言えば、やっぱり...
Ah, well, speaking of ShishiWata...
ぼたん様がわため様を、やっぱパックンちょしたいみたいな...
Botan-sama always wants to go "chomp" on Watame-sama...
あ、これね、いつもの感じじゃないですか、これね。
Oh, right. That's how it always is, isn't it?
いっつも召し上がるときって、どういう食べ方をされてるんですか？
When you eat me, what's your favorite way to do it?
わたくしの目の前で聞きます？
You're asking that right in front of me?
本人の目の前にして言うのもあれなんですけども...
It's a bit awkward to say it in front of her, but...
最近ちょっとおすすめの食べ方がありまして。
I have a recommended way to eat you lately.
ラムしゃぶです。
Lamb shabu!
ラムしゃぶ！？
Lamb shabu!?
次、ラムしゃぶかー...
So lamb shabu is next, huh...
最近までは焼くとかさ、普通に煮るとかだったと思うんですけど、
Lately it was just grilling or boiling, I think, but...
最近のブームは、ラムしゃぶなの。
the current trend is lamb shabu.
なるほどね、美味しい食べ方があるんだ。
I see, there's a delicious way to eat.
食べ方も色々ね、味変もできるしね、なるほどね。
You can eat it in different ways, like changing the flavor. I see.
じゃあチョコ先生もよかったら、今度からわためをこうやって、あーんってやってもらって。
So Choco-sen, if you'd like, go "ahh" to Watame like this from now on.
いいんですか！？
Is it okay!?
いいんですか！？食べちゃいますよ、食べちゃって！
Is it okay!? I'm going to eat you! Eat me up!
まあ今日はお祝いだからさ、いいから、一口ぐらいね。
Since it's a celebration today, just one bite.
あ、じゃあ真ん中に来てもらって。プレゼント...
Well then, please come to the center. For the present...
何？何？真ん中に来てもらって。主役だから。
What? What? Come to the center. Because you're the star.
だって今わたくしが、プレゼントって言おうとしたのに！
Since I was just about to say "present"!
だったらね、プレゼントは真ん中に来るのよ！プレゼントやぞ！
If it's a present, come to the center! It's a present!
ハッピーバースデー・ディア・チョコ先生〜
Happy birthday dear Choco-sen~
ハッピーバースデー・トゥー・ユー！
Happy birthday to you!
プレゼントです！
Present time!
いただきます！
I'm digging in!
怖いですよ！
Scary!
やっぱりね、食べられる運命だったんだよ、君は。
It was your destiny to be eaten, after all.
サイコパスだ！
You're a psychopath!
いや、ぼたん様一緒に食べちゃいましょう！食べちゃいましょう！
Botan-sama, let's eat together! Let's eat!
今がスクショタイムだぞ、みんな！
It's screenshot time, everyone!
みんなスクショだ、スクショ！
Take screenshots, everyone!
カメラ目線決めていく！いいよ！
Striking a pose for the camera! Nice!
ノルテの、ノルテのカメラ目線。
Noel's camera gaze.
まあね、これからももっとてぇてぇコンビが来るらしいからさ。
Look forward to more wholesome duos from now on.
楽しみに見とこうぜ。
Let's look forward to it.
見てよ。見てよ。
Watch it. Watch it.
はい、とりあえずね。頑張ってね、わためな、頑張ってな！
Alright, for now. Good luck, Watame, good luck!
本日はお腹いっぱいになりました！ありがとうございました！
I'm full now! Thank you very much!
バイバーイ！バイバーイ！バイバーイ！
Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
はい！ということでお次はどなたかな？
Alright! So who's next?
どうぞ！
Here we go!
ななな ななななななな ななな ななななな ななな...
Na na na...
我儘姫
Wagamama Hime (Selfish Princess)
わん、ふー、すりー
One, two, three
不思議なステップで踊りだすビート
Dancing to the beat with mysterious steps
今宵輝くネオンの下で光る
Shining under the neon tonight
わたくし可愛い召使い達
I'm cute, my servants
あの子はどこに？
Where is that girl?
うだうだごろごろだらだらにゃんにゃん
Idling, rolling around, lazing about, meow meow
何もしたくない
I don't want to do anything
甘い甘いチョコが食べたい
I want to eat sweet, sweet chocolate
アツアツなラテが飲みたい
I want to drink hot, hot latte
ホクホクなパン食べたいの
I want to eat warm, fluffy bread
トロットロのチーズが食べたい
I want to eat gooey cheese
フカフカのベッドに寝たい
I want to sleep in a soft, fluffy bed
そっとそっとおやすみなさい
Gently, gently, good night
わがままな La La La
Selfish La La La
誰も逆らわないで
Don't anyone defy me
わたくし可哀想でしょ
I'm pitiful, right?
お願いギギギ 全て与え続けて
Please give give give... keep giving me everything
何もかも許される
Everything is forgiven
だってわたくしが一番可愛いんだから
Because I'm the cutest of all
すりー、つー、わん
Three, two, one
香ばしい匂いで騒ぎ出すビート
The beat starts to bustle with a fragrant scent
今宵月明かりの下で
Tonight under the moonlight
Daydream 非日常 撮影日和
Daydream, unusual, perfect day for filming
お好きなオプションで
With your favorite options
誰もわたくしには適わない
No one can match me
つまらない
Boring
苦い苦い肝が食べたい
I want to eat bitter, bitter liver
赤い赤いスープ飲みたい
I want to drink red, red soup
フーフーお肉食べたいの
I want to eat sizzling meat
甘い甘い それじゃ足りない
Sweet, sweet, that's not enough
歪んだ Face もっと見せて
Show me more of your distorted face
まだまだ足りないわ
It's still not enough
わがままなわたくしのこと愛してくれる
You'll love me for my selfishness
誰かを待っているの
I'm waiting for someone
こんな夜更けに一人 枕を濡らして
All alone late at night, wetting my pillow with tears
秒針を眺めてる
I'm watching the second hand of the clock
だって私が
Because I'm...
わがまま
...selfish
Selfish
ランランラン 誰も壊さないで
La la la, please don't break anything
私可愛いでしょ
I'm cute, aren't I?
お願いギブギブミー 全て与え続けて
Please give, give me, keep giving me everything
何もかも許される
Everything is forgiven
やっぱ私が一番可愛いんだから
After all, I'm the cutest one
はーい！ということで！
All right! And so!
こんばんはー！
Good evening!
チョコチョコチョコチョコ...
Choco-choco-choco-choco...
なんでだよ！なんで逃げるんだ！
Why! Why are you running away!
逆だろお前！置いてきぼりにして！
You're the one! Leaving us behind!
どの口が言うんだ！お前は！踏み潰した！
Look who's talking! You! You stepped on me!
あ、ということでね。
Ah, and so.
今回はチョコはてぇてぇに挟まれたいということで！
This time, Choco wanted to be surrounded by preciousness!
ちょっとチョコの推しメン二人に来てもらいました！
So I asked two of my favorite members to come!
推しメンなんてそんなこと！お誕生日おめでとう！
Favorite members? Don't say that! Happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
あの、チョコ、お誕生日なんで...
Um, since it's Choco's birthday...
今日はわがまま言ってもいいですか？
Can I be a bit selfish today?
わがまま！わがまま姫なんだから！
Selfish! You're the Selfish Princess after all!
何ですか？わがままっていうのは。
What is it? This selfishness.
チョコ、みこちがはあちゃまにあの...
Choco wanted to see Mikochi being... um...
...困らされてるところを見たくて。
...troubled by Haachama.
待って。
Wait.
とりあえずぶった切られるのね。
So I'm just going to be cut off like that.
とりあえず、みこ様、サムネと同じポーズしてもらってもいいですか？
For now, Miko-sama, can you do the same pose as the thumbnail?
あ、はい、分かりました。
Ah, yes, I understand.
やだー！
Nooo!
なんでだよ！おかしいだろ！
Why! That's weird!
はあちゃま、お豆腐いいね。
Haachama, nice tofu.
嫌ではないかもしれない、もはや。
I might not even hate it anymore.
ちょ、ちょっと、いい、いい！
Wait, wait, good, good!
めちゃめちゃいい！
It's really good!
嘘だろ！やめて、はあちゃま！
You gotta be kidding! Stop it, Haachama!
あ、じゃあ私がこうやってるんで、はあちゃまじゃあ好きなふり蹴り飛ばすでもなんでもしてもらって。
Ah, then I'll stay like this, so Haachama, feel free to kick or whatever you like.
やめろよ！
Stop it!
ひどい、これが見たかったの。
Terrible, this is what I wanted to see.
美味しい、ラブラブとかじゃないの。
Delicious, it's not like lovey-dovey or anything.
あれ、思ってたのと違うなチョコ。
Wait, this is different from what I thought, Choco.
ラブラブとかじゃないんだね。
It's not lovey-dovey then.
おお、いや、ここはなんか、振り回されるのがいいかなって。
Oh, well, I thought being pushed around would be good here.
そっか。まあ、まあ、まあ。
I see. Well, well, well.
金髪の二人に囲まれたみこもなかなか...
Miko being surrounded by two blondes is also quite something...
あ、じゃあ挟まっていただいて、みこ様。
Ah, then please sandwich her, Miko-sama.
あ、いいんですか？金髪なら誰でもいいんか？
Ah, is it okay? Is anyone okay as long as they're blonde?
誰でもよくないよ！
Not anyone!
や、嬉しいなー。
Well, I'm happy.
じゃあ、可愛く。
Now, look cute.
パシャ。
Click.
あ、チョコ先生、いいな。
Ah, Choco-sensei, nice.
あ、チョコ先生のポニテいいな。
Ah, Choco-sensei's ponytail is nice.
ほんと？
Really?
ポニテ、あ、ポニテにするか。
Ponytail, ah, should I go with a ponytail?
え、何、みこに気を引いてるのか？
Eh, what, are you trying to get Miko's attention?
可愛い。
Cute.
いや、でもねチョコ先生、この後もね。
No, but you know, Choco-sensei, after this too...
ゲストがまだまだいるんですよね。
There are still more guests, right?
はい。
Yes.
じゃあ最後にチョコ先生、この後も頑張って大好きって言ってもらっていいですか？
Then finally, Choco-sensei, can you say "keep working hard after this too, I love you"?
チョコ先生、この後も頑張って！大好き！
Choco-sensei, keep working hard after this too! We love you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
女子校戦争
Girls' School War
作詞 ゆう 作曲 samfree
High School Girl War
Lyrics: Yuu Composition: samfree
チャイムのベルぎりぎりで
Right at the chime of the bell
ノーメイク別人の顔で
With a no-makeup face of someone else
すいませ すいませ すいませんね
Sorry, sorry, so sorry
まぶた重い
My eyelids are heavy
教科書の隅に書いた
Written in the corner of the textbook
おくちに潜む魔物
A monster lurking in my mouth
すいませ すいませ 吸い込まれる
Sorry, sorry, I'm being sucked in
片思い
One-sided love
3限過ぎればだいたいみんな本気を出してガチ滅
After the 3rd period, everyone usually gets serious and goes all out
まじだるジャージがスカートから覗くそこは桃源郷
Really tiring jerseys peeking from under skirts, that's Shangri-la
女子校戦争鳴り止まない 美しい花園なんかじゃない
High school girl war won't stop ringing, it's not a beautiful flower garden
みんな獲物狙っている テリトリー邪魔させない
Everyone is eyeing their prey, won't let you interfere with my territory
女子校戦争負けられない あのイケメン教師落としたい
High school girl war, I can't lose, I want to seduce that handsome teacher
制服脱ぎもほどいたらな カウントダウン始まるわ
Once I've loosened my uniform, the countdown begins
期末テストぎりぎりで
Right at the end of the final exams
意味なく手を上げアピール
Pointlessly raising my hand to appeal
すいませ すいませ すいませんね
Sorry, sorry, so sorry
上目遣い
Looking up with puppy eyes
教室の隅に寄せた
Pushed to the corner of the classroom
補習に潜む魔物
A monster lurking in the supplementary lessons
すいませ すいませ 吸い込まれる
Sorry, sorry, I'm being sucked in
子供扱い
Being treated like a child
数学・物理の時だけ本気を出して含める
I only get serious during math and physics
まじだる仮病使い呼び出し口実そこは桃源郷
Really tiring faking illnesses to get called out, that's Shangri-la
女子校戦争鳴り止まない 麗しい花園なんかじゃない
High school girl war won't stop ringing, it's not a lovely flower garden
みんな火花を散らしている 抜け駆けは許されない
Everyone is flying sparks, no one is allowed to get ahead
女子校戦争負けられない あのあざとい女子を蹴落としたい
High school girl war, I can't lose, I want to kick down that devious girl
制服のボタン外したらな カウントダウン始まるわ
Once I've undone my uniform button, the countdown begins
ねえ 先生 教えて
Hey, teacher, tell me
方程式が解けないの
I can't solve the equation
ねえ 先生 助けて
Hey, teacher, help me
あたし熱があるみたい
It seems I have a fever
女子校戦争鳴り止まない 美しい花園なんかじゃない
High school girl war won't stop ringing, it's not a beautiful flower garden
みんな獲物狙っている テリトリー邪魔させない
Everyone is eyeing their prey, won't let you interfere with my territory
女子校戦争負けられない あのイケメン教師落としたい
High school girl war, I can't lose, I want to seduce that handsome teacher
制服の裾めくったらら 子供扱いさせないわ
Once I've flipped up the hem of my uniform, I won't let you treat me like a child
女子校～！
High school girls~!
戦争～！
War~!
お疲れ様でした～！
Thank you for the hard work~!
じゃあね、今日はね
Well then, today...
何？何？何？
What? What? What?
お誕生日ということで、ルーナさん
Since it's your birthday, Luna-san...
ちょっとプレゼントをあげますか
Shall we give you a little present?
プレゼント！
A present!
チョコ先生、どんなものが欲しいなら？
Choco-sensei, what kind of thing do you want?
えっ、チョコ先生、全力で
Eh, Choco-sensei, with all my might...
プレゼント、どうぞー！
Here's your present!
違う違う！そんな強くない、そんな強くない！
No, no! Not that strong, not that strong!
行け行け行け！
Go go go!
怖い怖い怖い！
Scary scary scary!
チョコ先生！
Choco-sensei!
スバルのものなのらー！
She's Subaru's!
全然強くない！全然強くない！
Not strong at all! Not strong at all!
抜け駆けは許されないのら！
No getting ahead!
チョコ先生、今日誕生、今日誕生...
Choco-sensei, today's birthday, today's birthday...
チョコ先生！
Choco-sensei!
チョコ先生、退治！退治！
Choco-sensei, exterminate! Exterminate!
いや嘘でしょ！
No, you're kidding!
ちょっと！
Wait a minute!
何よ！もう！
What is it! Jeez!
あっち行ってよ！
Go away!
何でアンタ...
Why are you...
さっきとキャラ違うじゃん！
Your character is different from before!
な、なによ！
W-What!
これくらいでいいのよ！
This is enough!
うそ！
No way!
そんなことないですよ！
That's not true!
ちょこ先生！
Choco-sensei!
わざと倒れたの？
Did you fall on purpose?
そんなこと！
Not at all!
倒れるでしょ普通！
Anyone would fall!
押されたら！
If they were pushed!
何やってんだよ！
What are you doing!
ということで じゃあもういいかな？
So, is that enough then?
えっ？
Eh?
じゃあもうご褒美はこんな感じでいいかな？
So, is this kind of reward okay?
奪い合ってたのに...
Even though we were fighting over you...
じゃあ帰りまーす！
Well, I'm going home!
えっ、帰っちゃうの？
Wait, you're leaving?
帰っちゃうのね本当に！
Are you really leaving!
何だよー！
What the heck!
行って欲し...
I want you to...
やだ、寂しい寂しい寂しい！
No, I'm lonely, lonely, lonely!
置いていかないで！
Don't leave me behind!
動きがやばい！
Your movements are crazy!
寂しいよ！置いてかないで！
I'm lonely! Don't leave me!
どんな動きだよそれ！
What kind of movements are those!
でもこの後まだまだ続くんですよね！
But there's still more after this, right!
まだまだ続きます！
Yes, there's still more!
この後はどんな感じで続くんですか？
How will it continue after this?
この後は...
After this...
まあね、スバルンナが補充できたから
Well, since I was able to recharge on Subarunna,
まあ最後まで突っ走ろうかなって思います！
I think I'll keep going until the end!
じゃあこのままねバリバリに突き進むという感じで！
Then, keep going full throttle!
頑張って！
Good luck!
ちょこ先生頑張って！
Do your best, Choco-sensei!
何でお前投げやりなんだよ！
Why are you being so half-hearted!
じゃあせっかくだから写真でも撮って応援しましょうか！
Well then, let's take a photo and cheer her on!
じゃあハート作って真ん中に入れてあげようよ！
Let's make a heart and put her in the middle!
あ、じゃあ入れるわね！
Oh, then I'll put her in!
あー！本当に！
Ah! Really!
あー幸せ...
Ah, I'm so happy...
てか丸になっちゃった！
Wait, it became a circle!
えっ、待って待って待って！
Wait, wait, wait!
ちょっとちゃんと作ってくださいよ！
Come on, make it properly!
何やってんの！
What are you doing!
はい！じゃあこれでね、ちょこ先生が頑張れますように！
There! Now, I hope this helps Choco-sensei do her best!
ちょこ先生頑張って！
Choco-sensei, do your best!
んみ頑張る！
I'll do my best!
よし！じゃあ帰るか！
Alright! Shall we go home then!
あー幸せー！
Ah, so happy!
素で言ってるからもう分からん...
She's saying it so casually, I don't know anymore...
あっち帰るか！
Let's go back over there!
またねー！
See ya!
頑張ってねー！
Good luck!
Snow halation
不思議だね 今の気持ち
It's strange, my feelings right now
空から降ってきたみたい
Seem as if they've fallen from the sky
特別な季節の色が
The colors of this special season
ときめきを見せるよ
Are making my heart throb
初めて出会った時から
Ever since we first met,
予感に騒ぐ心のメロディ
A premonition makes the melody in my heart stir
とめられない とまらない なぜ
I can't stop it, it won't stop, why?
届けて 切なさには
Deliver it! To this heartache,
名前をつけようか “Snow halation”
Shall we give a name? "Snow halation"
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap,
待てずに 悔しいけど好きって純情
I can't wait... It's frustrating, but love is pure
微熱の中 ためらってもダメだね
In this slight fever, it's no use hesitating
飛び込む勇気に賛成 まもなくStart!!
I agree with the courage to dive in! It's starting soon!!
音もなく気配もなく
Without a sound, without a sign,
静かに運命は変わる
Fate quietly changes
これからの未来に胸の
The future ahead makes my chest
鼓動が早くなる
Beat faster
例えば困った時には
For instance, when I'm in trouble,
すぐ駆けつけて抱きしめたくて
I want to rush to you and hold you tight
どこにいても どこでも My high
Wherever you are, anywhere, my high
急いで いつの間にか
Hurry up! Before I knew it,
大きくなりすぎた “True emotion”
My "True emotion" grew too big
夢だけ見てるようじゃ
If I only see dreams,
辛いよ 恋人は君って言いたい
It's painful... I want to say my lover is you
優しい目が とまってる イヤだよ
Your gentle eyes are fixed on me... I don't want that!
このまま一気に愛情 あずけて Please!!
Let me entrust all my love to you at once, please!!
Snow halation
届けて 切なさには
Deliver it, to this sorrow
名前をつけようか Snow halation
Shall we give it a name? Snow halation
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap
待たずに 悔しいけど好きって純情
Without waiting... It's frustrating, but 'I love you' is pure heart
微熱の中 ためらってもダメだね
In this slight fever, hesitating is no good
飛び込む勇気に賛成
I'm for the courage to dive in
まもなく Start!!
It's starting soon!!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
チョコ先生おめでとうございます！
Choco-sensei, congratulations!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
チョコ先生、なんで我々呼んでくれたんですか？
Choco-sensei, why did you invite us?
確かに。なんでぺこまりなんだろうって思って。
True. I was wondering why it's Peko-Mari.
今回は、ちょっとてぇてぇに挟まれたい。
This time, I wanted to be sandwiched between 'te-te'.
てぇてぇ？
Te-te (wholesome)?
うちら？うちらてぇてぇ？
Us? We're 'te-te'?
遠いですよ！てぇてぇから！
We're so far from being 'te-te'!
自覚がもしかしてない、お二人さん。
Maybe you two just lack self-awareness.
ぺこらちゃんが鈍感なんだから。マリンの気持ちに気づいてないんだわ。
Pekora-chan is just being dense. She hasn't noticed Marine's feelings yet.
おかしい、おかしい！
Wait, that's not right!
チョコ先生マジで、あれぺこですよ。
Choco-sensei, seriously... that's not us.
ぺこまりてぇてぇって言われないぺこですよ本当にちょっと。
We're really not called 'Peko-Mari te-te'.
言われてる！
Yes, you are!
ちょっと待って2対1になってる！
Wait, wait, it's two against one!
言われてます！
You definitely are!
聞いたことないぺこですよ！
I've never heard that, Peko!
自覚なくたっていいのよ、ぺこらちゃん。
It's fine if you don't realize it, Pekora-chan.
ぺこらがそのムーブすればするほどね、なんかね...
The more Pekora makes those moves...
普段はこうやってそっけなくしてるけど、実はマリン好きぺこなんだよ。
Usually you're so cold, but actually you love Marine, Peko!
てぇてぇなんです！
That's 'te-te'!
エゴサでもぺこまりてぇてぇなんて隣で書かれてること一度も見たことないぺこですから！
Even when I search, I've never seen 'Peko-Mari te-te' written anywhere, Peko!
チョコ先生目を覚ましていただいていいぺこですか！
Choco-sensei, please wake up, Peko!
違う違う。
No, no.
こうやってね、塩対応を...
Like this, this salty response...
塩対応を解凍するかのようなてぇてぇね。
It's like wholesome 'te-te' that melts your salty attitude.
ぺこらちゃんなんですけど、本当はね...
Pekora-chan is like this, but deep down...
もうちょっと構ってもらいたいから塩対応してるわけ。
She wants more attention, so she acts salty.
違う、違う！
No, no way!
勝手なこと言わないでくださいよ、本当にもう！捏造やめてよ！
Don't just say whatever you want! Stop making things up!
なんなのもうこれ！
What is even going on!
でもチョコ先生の誕生日なんですよ。
But it's Choco-sensei's birthday.
求められてるものをさ、サービスで提供するのが我々の仕事でしょ。
Providing what's requested is our job, isn't it?
そうぺこだけど...
That's true, but...
じゃあチョコ先生も混ぜて、ぺこまりチョコてぇてぇにしないぺこですか？
Then why don't we include Choco-sensei and do 'Peko-Mari-Choco te-te'?
あ、混ぜてね。
Oh, include me too.
なるほどね、こういうことか。
I see, like this.
これだー！
This is it!
チョコ先生好きぺこだよ！
Choco-sensei, I love you, Peko!
好きぺこだよ！大好きだよチョコ！
I love you, Peko! I love you, Choco!
チョコ大好きです！
I love Choco so much!
あ、これでいいんだ、挟まる感じで。
Ah, this is perfect, being sandwiched like this.
これがてぇてぇぺこね、今日は挟まれてるからチョコ。
This is what 'te-te' is, Peko. Today, Choco is surrounded.
強引だよちょっと！
That's a bit forced!
邪道だよあんたのは！
What you're doing is wrong!
誕生日だからこそ許されるのよ、このてぇてぇに挟まれるのは。
It's only allowed because it's my birthday, being surrounded by 'te-te'.
誕生日じゃなきゃここ行ったらもうね、めちゃくちゃ叩かれるから。
If it wasn't a birthday, I'd get bashed for doing this.
叩く？
Bash?
叩かねぇよ！
Nobody's gonna bash you!
どうですか？幸せですかチョコ先生。
So, how is it? Are you happy, Choco-sensei?
すごいすごいニヤニヤしてるぺこですよ。
Look at that, she's grinning so much, Peko.
でも思ってるよりぺこらが冷めてることに気づいてしまったな。
But I realized Pekora is colder than I thought.
マリンチョコ先生といちゃいちゃしよ。
I'll go flirt with Choco-sensei instead.
え？
Eh?
やめろな！配信者の誕生日なんだからやめろな本当にもう。
Stop it! This is a YouTuber's birthday, so stop it already!
あら、嫉妬かな、ぺこらちゃん。
Oh, are you jealous, Pekora-chan?
違う！
No!
ぺこらちゃんもてぇてぇされたいの？
Do you want to be part of the 'te-te' too?
よしよし、混ぜて混ぜて。
There, there, come and join us.
あー、嬉しい。
Ah, I'm so happy.
ありがとう二人とも。
Thank you, both of you.
楽しかったです！
It was fun!
チョコ先生まだまだあるんでしょ。
Choco-sensei, there's still more, right?
まだまだあります！
Yes, there is!
頑張ってぺこ！
Good luck, Peko!
次はどこに挟まれに行くのかなチョコ先生。
Where are you going to get sandwiched next, Choco-sensei?
確かに気になる、ふふふ。
I'm curious too, hehe.
次は最後のてぇてぇなんで。
The next one is the final 'te-te'.
おー！
Oh!
じゃあ次の挟まれ先に行ってる間に...
Well then, while you head to your next sandwich spot...
邪魔者がいなくなったぺこら二人きりだ。
Now that the intruder's gone, it's just the two of us, Pekora.
ちょっと待って、邪道だ！
Wait a minute, that's not right!
違う、行くよマリンちゃん、本当にもう。
No, let's go, Marine-chan. Honestly!
行ってきまーす！
Off I go!
このあともお楽しみに！
Please look forward to what's coming next!
大胆不敵にハイカラ革命
Bold and fearless, a modern revolution
磊々落々反戦国家
A massive, open anti-war nation
日の丸印の二輪車転がし
Rolling along on a bicycle with the Hinomaru mark
悪霊退散 ICBM
Exorcising evil spirits, ICBM
環状線を走り抜けて
Running through the loop line
東奔西走なんのその
Going east and west, it's no big deal
少年少女戦国無双
Boys and girls, Sengoku Musou
浮世の随に
At the mercy of the floating world
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ
Senbonzakura, disappearing into the night
君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
Not even your voice will reach
此処は宴 鋼の檻
This is a banquet, a cage of steel
その断頭台で見下ろして
Looking down from that guillotine
三千世界 常世の闇
Three thousand worlds, the darkness of the eternal world
嘆ク唄モ聞コエナイヨ
Not even the lamenting song can be heard
青藍の空 遥か彼方
The deep blue sky, far, far away
その光線銃で打ち抜いて
Shoot through it with that ray gun
百戦錬磨の見た目は将校
A veteran of a hundred battles, looking like an officer
いったりきたりの花魁道中
Coming and going, the courtesan procession
アイツもコイツも皆で集まれ
That guy, this guy, everyone gather round
聖者の行進 ワンツーさんし
The saints' march, one-two-three-four
禅定門を潜り抜けて
Passing through the gateway to Zen
安楽浄土厄払い
Exorcising bad luck for a peaceful paradise
きっと最後は大団円
Surely the end will be a grand finale
拍手の合間に
In the midst of the applause
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ
Senbonzakura, disappearing into the night
君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
Not even your voice will reach
此処は宴 鋼の檻
This is a banquet, a cage of steel
その断頭台で見下ろして
Looking down from that guillotine
三千世界 常世の闇
Three thousand worlds, the darkness of the eternal world
嘆ク唄モ聞コエナイヨ
Not even the lamenting song can be heard
希望の丘 遥か彼方
The hill of hope, far, far away
その閃光弾を打ち上げろ
Fire that flashbang
環状線を走り抜けて
Running through the loop line
東奔西走なんのその
Going east and west, it's no big deal
少年少女戦国無双
Boys and girls, Sengoku Musou
浮世の随に
At the mercy of the floating world
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ
Senbonzakura, disappearing into the night
君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
Not even your voice will reach
此処は宴 鋼の檻
This is a banquet, a cage of steel
その断頭台を飛び降りて
Jump down from that guillotine
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ
Senbonzakura, disappearing into the night
君が歌い僕は踊る
You sing and I dance
此処は宴 鋼の檻
This is a banquet, a cage of steel
さあ光線銃を撃ちまくれ
Now, fire that ray gun like crazy
はーい、ということで！
All right, and with that!
ちょこ先生誕生日おめでとうー！！
Happy birthday, Choco-sensei!!
おめでとうー！！
Congratulations!!
嬉しい～
I'm so happy~
ね、今日はあれ、てぇてぇに囲まれたくて私らを呼んだとか？
So, did you invite us because you wanted to be surrounded by precious vibes?
あ、そうですやっぱりね。
Ah, yes, that's right.
このお二人はフブミオでね、もう長年の絆でもう...
You two are 'FubuMio', and with your long-standing bond...
...絡み合って、絡み合って、絡み合って、深い絆で結ばれてるみたいな...
...entwined, entwined, entwined together, that deep sense of connection you share...
...信頼感がめちゃめちゃ好きで。
...that mutual trust is something I absolutely love.
あー、なるほどなー。
Ah, I see, I see.
ちょっとその間に、1回人生で一度だけ...
I thought that just once in my life...
...入ってみたいと思って、ちょっと召喚しちゃいました。
...I'd like to be right in the middle of that, so I summoned you here.
なるほどねー。
I see, I see.
じゃあ、ちょこ先生になんかてぇてぇ供給したほうがいいってことだよね？
So that means we should provide you with some precious moments, right?
あ、そういうこと？
Oh, is that how it is?
えー見せてくれるんですか！？
Wait, you're going to show me!?
てぇてぇを！どうしよう...
Those precious vibes! Oh my gosh...
どうすればいいんだ、これ
What should we do about this?
え〜、なんだろう、なんだろう
Hmm, what could it be, what could it be?
毛づくろいでもしようか、じゃあ
Shall we do some grooming then?
毛づくろいでもしようか
Shall we do some grooming?
あら〜、毛づくろいよ、毛づくろいよ、じゃあ
Oh, grooming time, grooming time then.
よしよしよし、よしよしよし…
There, there, there, there, there, there...
ミオのすごいからね、もう、あれ
Mio's is amazing, you know, that thing.
すごいからね、もう
It's amazing, already.
あれ？なんかペットみたいな扱いじゃないですか？
Wait? Aren't we being treated like pets?
悪くはないですが
It's not bad, though.
え、もしかして、うちらのことペットだと思ってますか？
Wait, by any chance, do you think of us as pets?
え、もしかして、今日チョコの家に来てくれるんですか？
Eh, could it be you're coming to Choco's house today?
え〜、そんな、そんな
Oh, no way, no way.
やばい、お持ち帰りされるこれ
This is bad, we're being taken home.
ペットとして迎えられるこれ
We're being welcomed as pets.
てか今日のゲストなんか、やたらケモ耳多かった気がしないでもないな
I can't help but feel there were a lot of beast ears among today's guests.
あ、そういうこと？
Ah, is that it?
そういうことか
So that's it.
やだ、でもチョコ、可愛いものには、ちょっと貢ぎ体質で、お世話したくなっちゃって
No, but Choco has a bit of a giving nature for cute things and just wants to take care of them.
やばい、チョコにお世話されるの…
This is bad, being taken care of by Choco...
チョコのご飯美味しいよね
Choco's food is delicious, isn't it?
ペット…やべ、ペット…チョコのご飯食べれる…
Pet... wait, pet... we get to eat Choco's food...
あ、でもチョコのご飯、美味しい、美味しいけど
Ah, but Choco's food is delicious, delicious but...
お腹満たされるけど
It fills our bellies, but...
三食昼寝付きが保証されて、チョコの朝昼晩の手料理がついてて
Three meals and a nap are guaranteed, with Choco's home cooking for breakfast, lunch, and dinner...
あ、それは食べたい…まま、美味しいけど、でも…
Ah, I want to eat that... well, it's delicious, but...
お風呂もちゃんと入れてあげるから
I'll give you a bath properly too.
お〜、でもちょっと、あの、狐と狼はペットに向かないので、大丈夫です
Oh, but foxes and wolves aren't really suited to being pets, so we're okay.
そうですね、向かないので
That's right, we're not suited for it.
やだ、悪魔だからそんなの関係ないわ
No, I'm a demon, so that doesn't matter.
やばい
This is bad.
どうしようこれ、逃げたほうがいいんじゃないこれ
What should we do? Shouldn't we run away?
捕まったら大変
It'll be bad if we get caught!
身ぐるみ剥がされちゃう
We'll be stripped of everything!
やばい、やばい、逃げろー！
Bad, bad, run away!
あ、待って、ちょっと待って！あ〜
Ah, wait, wait a minute! Ah...
逃げられちゃった
They ran away.
おかしいな、チョコ、ちょっといい福利厚生用意したと思ったんだけどな
That's strange. Choco thought I prepared some pretty good benefits.
しょうがない
Well, can't be helped.
はい、ということで、この後はね
Alright, so after this...
ま、ここでゲストパートは終わりなのですが
Well, the guest part ends here, but...
まだまだ重大発表残っているので、お楽しみに！
There are still major announcements left, so look forward to it!
みんなは逃げないでね
Don't you guys run away.
そのまま、ちゃんといい子に待っててね
Stay there and wait like good kids.
またね
See you later.
どりーみんチュチュ
作詞・作曲 emon(Tes.)
Dreamin' Chuchu
Lyrics/Composition: emon(Tes.)
恋心 実らせた
My love has borne fruit
純情可憐な女の子
A pure and lovely girl
目の下クマクマ コンシーラー
Dark circles under my eyes, concealer
あ、なんてったって今日はバレンタイン
Ah, after all today is Valentine's
鈍いあいつもチラチラ
Even that dense guy is glancing
さすがに意識してるみたい
It seems he's finally noticed
火の無い二人に火を灯せ
Light a fire for the two of us without fire
今日はそうだね 特別な日さ
That's right, today is a special day
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコラタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu Choco-la-ta-ta-ta
スウィートな魔法を君だけに
A sweet magic just for you
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコラタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu Choco-la-ta-ta-ta
そのハートに届けたいな
I want to reach that heart
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコラタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu Choco-la-ta-ta-ta
ビターな甘さで包んでね
Envelop it in bitter sweetness
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコラタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu Choco-la-ta-ta-ta
チョコラタタタ
Choco-la-ta-ta-ta
放課後 屋上で待ち合わせ
Meeting up on the rooftop after school
ドキドキ 鼓動が高鳴る
My heart is pounding fast
階段 昇る君の足音が
The sound of your footsteps coming up the stairs
私の体を震わせた
Made my body tremble
向かい合う二人
The two of us facing each other
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコラタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu Choco-la-ta-ta-ta
スウィートな魔法を君だけに
A sweet magic just for you
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコラタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu Choco-la-ta-ta-ta
そのハートに届けたいな
I want to reach that heart
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコラタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu Choco-la-ta-ta-ta
ビターな甘さで包んでね
Envelop it in bitter sweetness
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコラタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu Choco-la-ta-ta-ta
チョコラッタッタッタ　チョコラッタッタッタ
Choco-lat-ta-ta-ta, Choco-lat-ta-ta-ta
私のココロとキミのココロ
My heart and your heart
キミのココロと私のココロ
Your heart and my heart
その距離を繋ぐチョコレート
The chocolate that connects that distance
夢の中で何度も描いたこの時は
In my dreams, this moment I've drawn so many times
世界にひとつだけだよ
It's the only one in the world
この瞬間　キミだけのために
This moment, just for you
スウィートなこの気持ち
This sweet feeling
送るからね　受け止めてね
I'm sending it to you, so please accept it
どりーみんチュチュ　チョコラッタッタッタ
Dreaming Chu Chu, Choco-lat-ta-ta-ta
スウィートな甘さをキミだけに
A sweet sweetness just for you
どりーみんチュチュ　チョコラッタッタッタ
Dreaming Chu Chu, Choco-lat-ta-ta-ta
そのハートに届けたいな
I want it to reach your heart
どりーみんチュチュ　チョコラッタッタッタ
Dreaming Chu Chu, Choco-lat-ta-ta-ta
ぴかぴかな魔法で包んでね
Wrap it in sparkling magic
どりーみんチュチュチュ　チョコラッタッタッタ　チョコラッタッタッタ　チョコラッタッタッタ
Dreaming Chu Chu Chu, Choco-lat-ta-ta-ta, Choco-lat-ta-ta-ta, Choco-lat-ta-ta-ta
はい！ということで！
Yes! And with that!
ゲストパートとソロパート、皆様いかがだったでしょうかー？
How did everyone enjoy the guest part and solo part?
まあね、どりーみんチュチュを歌ったということは、まあ皆様もお察しがついてるかと思うんですけど...
Well, singing Dreaming Chu Chu, I think you've all probably guessed...
まあ今日はね、バレンタインデーということで、まあちょこの誕生日でもあり、バレンタインデーということでね...
Well, today is Valentine's Day, which is also Choco's birthday, so...
ちょこから愛のこもったプレゼントを皆様に告知したいと思いまーす！ということで！
I'd like to announce a present filled with love from Choco to everyone! So!
な、な、な、なんと！今年も出ます！癒月ちょこお誕生日グッズ！ということでね！
W-w-w-what! They're coming out again this year! Yuzuki Choco Birthday Goods! So!
それでは早速ご紹介行きたいと思います！
Now, let's get straight to the introduction!
まずは、こちら！
First, this!
ドドドドドドー！こちらね、癒月ちょこ玄関カーテンということでね！
Dadadadadada! This is the Yuzuki Choco entrance curtain!
いや今回、ちょこすごい迷ったの。グッズ何にしようかなーって。
Actually, Choco was really undecided this time. About what the goods should be.
今回はちょこ先生のお使いグッズにしました！
This time, I decided on 'Choco-sensei's Errands' goods!
そしてね、この玄関カーテン。いや皆様ね、もうこれ分かるんじゃないですか、分かるんじゃないですか？
And this entrance curtain. Well everyone, you can probably tell, can't you?
ちょこ先生がお帰りって、お使い頼んで、お帰り、ありがとう、で迎えてくれてるね...
Choco-sensei saying 'Welcome back', having asked for an errand, 'Welcome back, thank you', greeting you...
はい、家に帰ったらなんと、ちょこ先生が出迎えてくれます！
Yes, when you get home, what do you know, Choco-sensei will be there to greet you!
この玄関カーテン、ぜひぜひね、皆様、まあ目隠しカーテンとしても使えるのでね、ご購入いただけたらと思います。
This entrance curtain, by all means, everyone, well it can also be used as a room divider, so I hope you'll buy it.
そしてもう一つ、こちら！たーん！
And another one, this! Ta-da!
ちょこらのコインケース！
Chocola coin case!
はい、こちらはねぜひぜひあの首から下げてね、あのちょこ先生からお使いもらったんだー、これに入れてお使い行くんだーってね、ぜひぜひ使ってください。
Yes, please hang this around your neck and use it, like 'I got an errand from Choco-sensei, I'm going to go do the errand with this'.
そしてね、こちらのトートバッグ！いやお使いのものをね、ぜひぜひ入れてね、皆様お持ち帰ってください。
And this tote bag! Please put your errand items in here and take them home with you.
そしてそして、今回も出てます！耳責めASMRボイス！ということでね！
And, and, it's out again this year! Ear-teasing ASMR voice! So!
一つ目のボイスが、寝落ちのお使いボイスということで。はい、寝落ちのね、あまあまなちょこ先生が甘えながらお使いを頼んでくるボイスです。
The first voice is the 'Falling Asleep Errands' voice. Yes, it's a voice where a very sweet Choco-sensei asks for an errand while being spoiled.
そして二つ目が、よく出来たねボイスということで。いやこちらはね、あの帰ってきて、ちょこ先生がお疲れありがとうって迎えてくれるあまあまボイスです。ご褒美もあるので、お楽しみに。
And the second is the 'You did a good job' voice. Well, this is a very sweet voice where Choco-sensei greets you with 'Good job, thank you' when you get back. There's also a reward, so look forward to it.
そしてね、こちらなんと！フルセットご購入の方のみ！
And here, what do you know! Only for those who buy the full set!
癒月ちょこ直筆サイン＆箔押しサイン入りポストカード！
Yuzuki Choco personally signed & foil-stamped postcard!
嘘つきました。えー、癒月ちょこ直筆サイン＆箔押しメッセージ入り！
I lied. Er, Yuzuki Choco personally signed & with a foil-stamped message!
なんと、Nardack先生描き下ろしのね、このイラストのポストカードがついてきます！
What do you know, you get a postcard with this illustration newly drawn by Nardack-sensei!
ちゃんと一枚一枚ちょこね、あのサイン書くのでね、ぜひぜひ皆様大切に保管してくださいね。
Choco will sign each and every one, so please keep them safe.
はい、そして特典ボイス！ちょこ先生とお使い通話！
Yes, and the bonus voice! An errand call with Choco-sensei!
ということでね、こちらはシチュエーションボイスとなっておりますが、なんと！なんと！ちょこ先生が通話でお使いを頼んでくるっていうね。しかも通話繋ぎながらお買い物ができるっていうボイスとなっておりますので、ぜひぜひ皆様お楽しみに。
So, this is a situation voice, but what do you know! Choco-sensei asks for an errand over a call. It's a voice where you can shop while being on a call with her, so please look forward to it.
それではね。
With that said...
グッズ告知はこの辺にしといて
Let's wrap up the goods announcement here.
この後は、もうひとつチョコからのお知らせがあるのですが
After this, I have one more announcement to make.
まずは、こちら。
First of all, this.
お知らせに行くには毎年恒例、レッドカーペット！
To get to the announcement, we have our annual tradition, the Red Carpet!
ということで、それでは皆様、チョコにいつものように...
And so, everyone, please do as you always do for Choco...
綺麗なね、赤いレッドカーペットを敷いて、道を作ってください。
...and lay down the beautiful red carpet to create a path.
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you very much!
それでは、レッドカーペット、スタート！
Alright then, Red Carpet, start!
はい、このレッドカーペットはね、毎年恒例と言いますか...
Yes, this Red Carpet is an annual tradition...
チョコの誕生日に欠かせないものとなっております。
...and has become an essential part of Choco's birthday.
はい、皆様からね、そう、その「おめでとう、おめでとう」ってなでてくれたものが...
Yes, all your "Congratulations, congratulations" messages that you've sent...
なんと、チョコに道を作ってくれるのです！
...will actually create a path for Choco!
はい、この後のね、みんなに用意したプレゼントに続く道なので...
Yes, this path leads to the presents I've prepared for you later...
ぜひぜひ参加していただけたら嬉しいです。
...so I'd be very happy if you could participate.
あ、それとさっき言い忘れちゃったんだけど...
Oh, and I forgot to mention this earlier...
あの、今回のグッズ、なんと21時5分からカートがオープンするので...
...but the cart for this time's goods will open at 21:05...
最後までゆっくり安心して見ててください。
...so please relax and enjoy until the end.
そしてね、今回チョコ、なんと、初めてね...
And also, Choco is actually, for the first time...
この配信の後にメン限ライブも、ちょっと...
...thinking of doing a membership-only live after this stream...
ちょっと考えちゃってるんで、よかったらね...
...so if you'd like...
21時15分からこの後メン限ライブもあるので、ぜひぜひ皆様...
...there'll be a membership live from 21:15, so please everyone...
まだね、メンバー登録してないよっていう方はね...
...if you haven't joined the membership yet...
この機会にメンバー登録よろしくお願いします！
...please take this opportunity to join! Thank you!
そして、そして、
And, and,
なんとね、皆様、このステージ...
...actually, everyone, this stage...
え、なんかいつもと違いませんか？
Eh, doesn't it look different than usual?
なんか魔界っぽくないですか？
Doesn't it look like the Demon World?
そう、今回、運営さんにお願いして、なんと、なんと...
Yes, this time I asked the staff, and...
チョコのね、お誕生日ステージ装飾、お願いして...
...asked them to decorate Choco's birthday stage...
「こちら」って見せたいんだけど、この先の方が綺麗に見えるから...
I want to show you, but it looks better from further ahead...
そこまで走らせてもらいたいなーって...
...so I'd like to run over there.
だだだだだ...
Running sounds...
みんな見てる？これ！
Is everyone seeing this!?
さっき言ってた運営さんに作ってもらったステージ、見てるみんな？
Are you all seeing the stage the staff made for me?
めちゃめちゃ凄くないですか！？
Isn't it absolutely amazing!?
そう、今回は魔界をちょっとイメージして、お願いしてみました。
Yes, I requested it with a Demon World theme in mind.
まあチョコ、悪魔なんでね、魔界命だから。
Well, Choco is a demon, so the Demon World is my life.
ということで、皆様、レッドカーペットもありがとうございました、なでていただいて。
So, thank you everyone for the red carpet and for all the petting.
そして、そして、もったいぶってたね、チョコからのプレゼントというか告知というやつは...
And now, for the present or announcement from Choco I've been teasing...
なんと、これから発表したいと思います！
...I'd like to announce it now!
ちょっとなんか恥ずかしいな。
I'm a little bit embarrassed.
それでは、聴いてください。新曲、
Now then, please listen to my new song,
「Sickbay Mistake」。
"Sickbay Mistake."
Sickbay Mistake
静かな午後 淡い日差し
A quiet afternoon, faint sunlight
カーテンが揺れる キミの声
The curtains sway, your voice
近づく足音だけで分かる
I can tell just by your approaching footsteps
さあ今日はどんな味がホ・シ・イ
Now, what kind of taste do you want today?
囁く悪魔の誘惑 What do you want?
The whispering demon's temptation, "What do you want?"
Ah... Sickbayで待ち合わせ Mistakeなヨカン
Ah... meeting at the Sickbay, a mistake-like feeling
扉開けてさあこっちへおいで
Open the door and come over here
教科書に載っていないこの気持ちは何ですか？
What is this feeling not written in textbooks?
可愛い可愛い顔みせて
Show me your cute, cute face
Sickbayで会いましょう Mistakeしちゃう？？
Let's meet at the Sickbay, will we make a mistake??
永遠に続け時間よ止まって
Continue forever, time please stop
教室じゃ見せられない笑顔の秘密は
The secret of the smile I can't show in the classroom is...
甘い甘いお菓子あげる
I'll give you sweet, sweet candy
囁く悪魔の誘惑いかが？
How about the temptation of a whispering devil?
秒針のリズム追い越してく
Overtaking the rhythm of the second hand
聴かせてもっとキミの鼓動
Let me hear your heartbeat more
触れる視線で身体中
With gazes that touch, throughout my body...
騒ぐのもうどうしようもないくらい
It's so loud, I can't help it
禁断の果実甘い もう後に戻れない
The forbidden fruit is sweet, there's no going back
目が合ってはにかんで触れ合って見つめ合って
Eyes meet, we're shy, we touch, we look at each other
永遠の楽園に誘う愛の言葉を
Love's words that invite us to an eternal paradise
耳元で囁いてあげる
I'll whisper them in your ear
Sickbayで待ってるわ Mistakeな時間
Waiting at the Sickbay, a mistake-like time
扉閉めてもっと近づいて
Close the door and come closer
神様も止められないこの気持ちの正体を
The true nature of this feeling that even God can't stop
知らないふりはもう出来ない
I can't pretend not to know anymore
Sickbayで会いたいの Mistakeしましょう
I want to meet at the Sickbay, let's make a mistake
永遠はここにあるって信じて
Believe that eternity is right here
キミにしか見せられない笑顔の裏側
The other side of the smile I can only show you
甘い甘い果実あげる
I'll give you sweet, sweet fruit
囁く悪魔の誘惑もっといかが？
How about more of the whispering devil's temptation?
いつでもここで待ってる My Cute student ♡
Waiting here anytime, My Cute student ♡
みんな、最後まで見てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for watching until the end!
この後はメン限ライブもあるので
After this, there's also a members-only live...
お楽しみに～！
So please look forward to it~!